Guide to the Native American subject vertical file [ca.1850-2000.]
Native American subject vertical file
- Music 1 (Box 86)
- Music 2 (Box 86)
- Music 3 (Box 134)
  Large amount of music from and about various tribes and individuals.
- Music - Articles & Corres. 1 (Box 86)
- Music - Articles & Corres. 2 (Box 86)
- Music - Instruments (Box 86)
- Music - Instruments - Articles & Corres. (Box 86)
- Muskhogean Indians (Box 86)
- Nahula (Box 86)
- Nambiquara Indians (Box 86)
- Names, Personal (Box 86)
- Names - Place (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Arizona (Box 86)
- Names - Place - California (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Canada (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Delaware (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Florida (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Georgia (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Idaho (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Illinois (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Iowa (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Louisiana (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Maine (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Massachusetts (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Mexico (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Michigan (Box 86)
- Names - Place - Middle America (Box 87)
- Names - Place - Minnesota (Box 87)
- Names - Place - Montana (Box 87)
- Names - Place - Nebraska (Box 87)
- Names - Place - New Hampshire (Box 87)
- Names - Place - New Jersey (Box 87)
- Names - Place - New Mexico (Box 87)
- Names - Place - New York (Box 87)
- Names - Place - North America (Box 87)
- Names - Place - Ohio (Box 87)
- Names - Place - Oklahoma (Box 87)
- Names - Place - Oregon (Box 87)
- Names - Place - Rhode Island (Box 87)
- Names - Place - South Dakota (Box 87)
- Names - Place - Texas (Box 87)
- Names - Place - Vermont (Box 87)
- Names - Place - Wyoming (Box 87)
- Nansemond Indians (Box 87)
- Nanticoke Indians (Box 87)
- Narcotics, Stimulants, and Alcohol 1 (Box 87)
- Narcotics, Stimulants, and Alcohol 2 (Box 87)
- Narragansett Indians (Box 87)
- Naskapi Indians (Box 87)
- Natchez Indians (Box 87)
- National Advisory Council on Indian Education (Box 132)
- National Archives Records (Box 87)
- National Indian Organizations (Box 132)
- National Museum of the American Indian (Box 87)
- Native American Church (Box 87)
- Natural Resources (Box 87)
- Natural Resources 2 (Box 132)
- Navajo Code Talkers (Box 87)
- Navajo Indians 1 (Box 87)
- Navajo Indians 2 (Box 87)
- Navajo Indians 3 (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians 4 (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians 5 (Box 132)
- Navajo Indians - Art (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Bibliography (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Bibliography - Articles & Corres. (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Crafts (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Crafts - Articles & Corres. (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Dwellings (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Economic development (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Economics (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Economics - clippins, etc. (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Education - clippings, etc. (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Government relations (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Health (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - History (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Hopi Land Disputes 1 (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Hopi Land Disputes 2 (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Legal Documents (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Legal Documents - Articles & Corres. (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Metals and Metalwork - Silver and Gold (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Navajo Program, 1935 (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Navajo Program - Religion & Mythology (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Relocation (Box 133)
- Navajo Indians - Rites and Ceremonies (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Rites and Ceremonies - Articles & Corres. (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Rugs (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Tribal Government (Box 88)
- Navajo Indians - Weaving and textiles (Box 89)
- Navajo Indians - Weaving and textiles - Articles & Corres. (Box 89)
- Nebraska (Box 89)
- Nebraska - Antiquities 1 (Box 89)
- Nebraska - Antiquities 2 (Box 89)
- Nebraska - History (Box 89)
- Nebraska - Indians (Box 89)
- Neutral Nation Indians (Box 89)
- Nevada - Antiquities (Box 89)
- Nevada - Bibliography (Box 89)
- Nevada - History (Box 89)
- Nevada - Indians (Box 89)
- Nevada - Indians - Legislation (Box 89)
- New Age Activities (Box 89)
- New England (Box 89)
- New England - Antiquities (Box 89)
- New England - History (Box 89)
- New England - Indians (Box 89)
- New Hampshire (Box 89)
- New Hampshire - Indians (Box 89)
- New Jersey (Box 89)
- New Jersey - Antiquities 1 (Box 90)
- New Jersey - Antiquities 2 (Box 90)
- New Jersey - History (Box 90)
- New Jersey - Indians (Box 90)
- New Mexico (Box 90)
- New Mexico 2 (Box 133)
  Antonio de Espejo, Extract from Espejo's narration, 1582-1583, typescript
- New Mexico 3 (Box 133)
  Antonio de Espejo, Expediente y relación del viaje que hizo Antonio Espejo con catorce soldados y un religioso de la orden de San Francisco, llamado Fray Agustín Rodríguez; el cual debía de entender en la predicación de aquella gente, ca. 1584, photostats.
- New Mexico 4 (Box 133)
  Antanio de Espejo, Entrada que hizo en el Nuevo Mexico, 1582, photostats.
- New Mexico 5 (Box 133)
  Juan Dominguez de Mendoza, Provincias internas, 37, photstats
- New Mexico 6 (Box 133)
  Joan de Onate, Discurso de la jornadas que higo el campo de su magestad desde la Neuva Espana a la provincia de la Nuevo Mexico, 1596, photostats.
- New Mexico 7 (Box 133)
  Joan de Onate, Treslado de la posesion que en nombre de su majestad tomo Don Joan de Onate de los reyos y provincias de la Nueva Mexico, 1589, photostats.
- New Mexico - Antiquities 1 (Box 90)
- New Mexico - Antiquities 2 (Box 90)
- New Mexico - Antiquities 3 (Box 90)
- New Mexico - Antiquities 4 (Box 90)
- New Mexico - Antiquities 5 (Box 91)
- New Mexico - Antiquities 6 (Box 91)
- New Mexico - Articles & correspondence (Box 91)
- New Mexico - Antiquities enchanted mesa (Box 91)
- New Mexico - History (Box 91)
- New Mexico - Indians 1 (Box 91)
- New Mexico - Indians 2 (Box 91)
- News Clippings (Box 133)
  Apparel, accounts, miscleaneous.
- New Sweden (Box 91)
- New York City - Documents and Records (Box 91)
- New York City - History (Box 91)
- New York City - Indians (Box 91)
- New York City - Indians - Articles, Corres., etc. (Box 91)
- New York City - Indians - Bronx (Box 92)
- New York City - Indians - Brooklyn, Queens (Box 92)
- New York City - Indians - Manhattan (Box 92)
- New York City - Indians - Staten Island (Box 92)
- New York State - Antiquities 1 (Box 92)
- New York State - Antiquities 2 (Box 92)
- New York State - Antiquities 3 (Box 92)
- New York State - Antiquities, Articles & Corres. (Box 92)
- New York State - History 1 (Box 92)
- New York State - History 2 (Box 92)
- New York State - History - Articles & Corres. (Box 92)
- New York State - Indians 1 (Box 92)
- New York State - Indians 2 (Box 93)
- New York State - Indians 3 (Box 93)
- New York State - Indians - Articles & Corres. (Box 93)
- New York State - Long Island (Box 93)
- New York State - Long Island - Antiquities (Box 93)
- New York State - Long Island - History (Box 93)
- New York State - Long Island - Indians (Box 93)
- Nez Perce Indians (Box 93)
- Nhumbiquara Indians - Brazil (Box 93)
- Niaua Indians (Box 93)
- Nicaragua (Box 93)
- Nicaragua - Antiquities (Box 93)
- Nicaragua - History (Box 93)
- Nicaragua - Indians (Box 93)
- Nice Tribes Area (Box 132)
- Nisqually Indians (Box 93)
- Nootka Indians - See also Language - Nootka (Box 93)
- North America - Indians (Box 93)
- North Carolina (Box 94)
- North Carolina - Antiquities (Box 94)
- North Carolina - History (Box 94)
- North Carolina - Indians (Box 94)
- North Dakota (Box 94)
- North Dakota - Antiquities (Box 94)
- North Dakota - History (Box 94)
- North Dakota - Indians - See also Missions - North Dakota (Box 94)
- Northeast (Box 94)
- Northwest Coast - Antiquities (Box 94)
- Northwest Coast - Art (Box 94)
- Northwest Coast Indians 1 (Box 94)
- Northwest Coast Indians 2 (Box 94)
- Northwest Coast Indians 3 (Box 94)
- Northwest Territory (Box 94)
- Ohio (Box 95)
- Ohio - Antiquities 1 (Box 95)
- Ohio - Antiquities 2 (Box 95)
- Ohio - Antiquities 3 (Box 95)
- Ohio - Antiquities 4 (Box 95)
- Ohio - Antiquities 5 (Box 95)
- Ohio - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. (Box 95)
- Ohio - History (Box 96)
- Ohio - Indians (Box 96)
- Ohio - River (Box 96)
- Ojo de Dios (Box 96)
- Oklahoma (Box 96)
- Oklahoma - Antiquities (Box 96)
- Oklahoma - History (Box 96)
- Oklahoma - Indians (Box 96)
- Olmecs (Box 96)
- Olympics, 1984 (Box 96)
- Omaha Indians 1 (Box 96)
- Omaha Indians 2 (Box 96)
- Ona Indians (Box 96)
- Oneida Indians (Box 97)
- Onondaga Indians (Box 97)
- Ontario - Antiquities (Box 97)
- Ontario - History (Box 97)
- Ontario - Indians (Box 97)
- Opata Indians (Box 97)
- Oral History (Box 97)
- Oratory (Box 97)
- Oregon (Box 97)
- Oregon - Antiquities (Box 97)
- Oregon - History (Box 97)
- Oregon - Indians 1 (Box 97)
- Oregon - Indians 2 (Box 97)
- Oregon - Indians - Legal documents (Box 97)
- Origins (Box 97)
- Osage Indians 1 (Box 97)
- Osage Indians 2 (Box 97)
- Osage Indians - Oversize (Box 131)
- Osage Indians - Legal documents (Box 97)
- Oto Indians (Box 97)
- Otomi Indians (Box 97)
- Ottawa Indians (Box 97)
- Ozark Mountain Region (Box 97)
- Pacific Islands (Box 97)
- Paez Indians (Box 97)
- Painting (Box 97)
- Paiute Indians (Box 98)
- Paiute Indians - Legal documents (Box 98)
- Paleopathology 1 (Box 98)
- Paleopathology 2 (Box 98)
- Pamunkey Indians (Box 98)
- Pan Indianism (Box 98)
- Panama (Box 98)
- Panama - Antiquities 1 (Box 98)
- Panama - Antiquities 2 (Box 98)
- Panama - History (Box 98)
- Panama - Indians (Box 98)
- Paraguay (Box 99)
- Paraguay - Indians (Box 99)
- Paramona Indians (Box 99)
- Parintintin Indians (Box 99)
- Passamaquoddy Indians (Box 99)
- Patwin Indians (Box 99)
- Paugussett (Box 99)
- Pawnee Indians 1 (Box 99)
- Pawnee Indians 2 (Box 99)
- Paya Indians (Box 99)
- Pennsylvania (Box 99)
- Pennsylvania - Antiquities 1 (Box 99)
- Pennsylvania - Antiquities 2 (Box 99)
- Pennsylvania - History 1 (Box 99)
- Pennsylvania - History 2 (Box 99)
- Pennsylvania - Indians (Box 100)
- Penobscot Indians (Box 100)
- Pen Pals (Box 133)
- Pequot Indians 1 (Box 100)
- Pequot Indians 2 (Box 100)
- Periodicals, Indian (Box 100)
- Peru 1 (Box 100)
- Peru 2 (Box 100)
- Peru 3 (Box 100)
- Peru - Antiquities 1 (Box 100)
- Peru - Antiquities 2 (Box 100)
- Peru - Antiquities 3 (Box 101)
- Peru - Antiquities 4 (Box 101)
- Peru - Antiquities 5 (Box 101)
- Peru - Antiquities 6 (Box 133)
  William Henry, Holmes, Textile fabrics of ancient Peru, 1889, photostats.
- Peru - Antiquities - Art (Box 101)
- Peru - Antiquities - English 1 (Box 101)
- Peru - Antiquities - English 2 (Box 101)
- Peru - Antiquities - English 3 (Box 101)
- Peru - Antiquities - French (Box 101)
- Peru - Antiquities - German 1 (Box 101)
- Peru - Antiquities - German 2 (Box 101)
- Peru - Antiquities - Spanish 1 (Box 101)
- Peru - Antiquities - Spanish 2 (Box 102)
- Peru - History (Box 102)
- Peru - Indians 1 (Box 102)
- Peru - Indians 2 (Box 102)
- Peru - Indians 3 (Box 102)
- Petroglyphs (Box 102)
- Petroglyphs - Rhode Island (Box 102)
- Peyote (Box 102)
- Phonograph Records (Box 102)
- Photography (Box 102)
- Physical Anthropology (Box 102)
- Pictographs (Box 102)
- Piegan Indians (Box 102)
- Pima Indians (Box 102)
- Pima Indians - Ethnology (Box 102)
- Pima Indians - Legal Articles (Box 103)
- Pima - Maricopa (Box 103)
- Pine Ridge Area (Box 132)
  Since Wounded Knee
- Piscataway Indians (Box 103)
- Plains - Antiquities (Box 103)
- Plains - Indians 1 (Box 103)
- Plains - Indians 2 (Box 103)
- Plains - Indians 3 (Box 103)
- Plains - Indians - Articles & Corres. etc. (Box 103)
- Plains - Indians - Art (Box 103)
- Plays and Pageants 1 (Box 103)
- Plays and Pageants 2 (Box 103)
- Plays and Pageants - Articles & Corres. (Box 103)
- Poetry (Box 104)
- Poetry - Articles & Corres. etc. (Box 104)
- Poisons (Box 104)
- Pokom Indians (Box 104)
- Political Activity (Box 104)
- Pollution, Radiation, etc. (Box 104)
- Pomo Indians (Box 104)
- Pomo Indians 2 (Box 133)
  Samuel Alfred Barrett, Pomo bear doctors, 1917, photostats of William Benson annotated copy.
- Ponca Indians (Box 104)
- Pontiac Indians (Box 104)
- Poosepatuck Indians (Box 104)
- Popolocas Indians (Box 104)
- Population - Before 1900 (Box 104)
- Population - Before 1900 2 (Box 133)
  S. N. Clark, Are the Indians dying out? Preliminary observations relating to Indian civilization and education, 1877, photostats.
- Population - 1900 - 1929 (Box 104)
- Population - 1930 - 1939 (Box 104)
- Population - 1940 - 1949 (Box 104)
- Population - 1950 - 1959 (Box 104)
- Population - 1960 - 1969 (Box 104)
- Population - 1970 - 1979 (Box 104)
- Population - 1980 - 1989 1 (Box 104)
- Population - 1980 - 1989 2 (Box 104)
- Population - 1990 - 1999 (Box 104)
- Population - General 1 (Box 104)
- Population - General 2 (Box 104)
- Postcards (Box 104)
- Potawatorni Indians (Box 104)
- Pottery 1 (Box 105)
- Pottery 2 (Box 105)
- Pottery - California (Box 105)
- Pottery - Central America (Box 105)
- Pottery - Central America and Mexico (Box 105)
- Pottery - Central and North America (Box 105)
- Pottery - Central and South America (Box 105)
- Pottery - Bibliographies (Box 105)
- Pottery - Descriptions and Techniques 1 (Box 105)
- Pottery - Descriptions and Techniques 2 (Box 105)
- Pottery - Northeast (Box 105)
- Pottery - Plains (Box 105)
- Pottery - Prehistoric Southwest 1 (Box 105)
- Pottery - Prehistoric Southwest 2 (Box 105)
- Pottery - Prehistoric Southwest (Anasazi, Hohokam, Mimbres) (Box 105)
- Pottery - Prehistoric Southwest (Maps) (Box 105)
- Pottery - South America (Ecuador and Brazil) (Box 105)
- Pottery - South America (Peru) (Box 105)
- Pottery - Southeast (Box 105)
- Pottery - Southwest 1 (Box 105)
- Pottery - Southwest 2 (Box 106)
- Pottery - Southwest Pueblo 1 (Box 106)
- Pottery - Southwest Pueblo 2 (Box 106)
- Pow - Wow (Box 106)
- Preservation 1 (Box 106)
- Preservation 2 (Box 106)
- Preservation - Conservation (Box 106)
- Prisons (Box 106)
- Protests 1 (Box 133)
- Protests 2 (Box 133)
  Gallup, New Mexico
- Protests 3 (Box 133)
  Trail of Broken Treaties
- Proper Names (Box 132)
- Psychology (Box 106)
- Public Opinion (Box 106)
- Publications 1 (Box 106)
- Publications 2 (Box 133)
- Publicity - Public Relations (Box 106)
- Pueblo Indians 1 (Box 106)
- Pueblo Indians 2 (Box 106)
- Pueblo Indians - Art (Box 106)
- Pueblo Indians - Articles & Misc. (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Corres. (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Government Relations - Bills (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Newspaper Articles (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Acoma (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Cochiti (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Isleta (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Jemez (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Laguna (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Nambe (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Picuris (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Pottery (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - San Felipe (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - San Ildefonso (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - San Juan (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Sandia (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Santa Ana (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Santa Clara (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Santo Domingo (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Taos 1 (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Taos 2 (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Tesuque (Box 107)
- Pueblo Indians - Zia (Sia) (Box 107)
- Puerto Rico (Box 107)
- Puerto Rico - Antiquities (Box 107)
- Puerto Rico - Antiquities - Articles & Corres. (Box 107)
- Quapaw Indians (Box 108)
- Quebec Indians (Box 108)
- Quechua Indians (Box 108)
- Querandi Indians (Box 108)
- Quiche Indians (Box 108)
- Quileute Indians (Box 108)
- Quilts (Box 108)
- Quinault Indians (Box 108)
- Quincentennary (Box 108)
- Quipus Indians (Box 108)
- Quivira Indians (Box 108)
- Radiocarbon Dating 1 (Box 108)
- Radiocarbon Dating 2 (Box 108)
- Rainforest (Box 108)
- Rama Indians (Box 108)
- Ramapo Indians (Box 108)
- Rappahannock Indians (Box 108)
- Records - LPs (Box 108)
- Red Power (Box 108)
- Red Power - Alcatraz 1 (Box 108)
- Red Power - Alcatraz 2 (Box 108)
- Red Power - B.I.A. (Box 108)
- Red Power - Historical Indians Point of View (Box 108)
- Red Power - Yellow Thunder Camp (Box 108)
- Refugee (Box 108)
- Religion 1 (Box 108)
- Religion 2 (Box 108)
- Religion 3 (Box 109)
- Religion 4 (Box 132)
- Religious Freedom (Box 109)
- Repatriation 1 (Box 109)
- Repatriation 2 (Box 109)
- Repatriation - laws and legislation (Box 109)
- Reproductions (Box 109)
- Research and Researchers (Box 109)
- Reservations 1 (Box 109)
- Reservations 2 (Box 109)
- Reservations 3 (Box 133)
- Reservations and Agencies (Box 109)
- Rhode Island (Box 109)
- Rhode Island - Antiquities (Box 109)
- Rhode Island - History (Box 109)
- Rhode Island - Indians (Box 110)
- Rock Art (Box 110)
- Rock Art - Correspondence, Newspaper Articles (Box 110)
- Rock Art - Petroglyphs 1 (Box 110)
- Rock Art - Petroglyphs 2 (Box 110)
- Rock Art - Petroglyphs 3 (Box 110)
- Rock Art - Pictographs (Box 110)
- Sacred Places (Box 110)
- Salish Indians 1 (Box 110)
- Salish Indians 2 (Box 110)
- Salish Indians - Oversize (Box 131)
- Salvador (Box 110)
- Salvador - Antiquities (Box 111)
- Salvador - Indians (Box 111)
- Sandpainting (Box 111)
- Santo Domingo (Box 111)
- Santos (Box 111)
- Saponi Indians (Box 111)
- Sarsi Indians (Box 111)
- Sauk and Fox Indians (Box 111)
- Save the Children Federation (Box 133)
- Scalping (Box 111)
- Schaghticoke (Box 111)
- Scholarships and Programs (Box 111)
- Schools (Box 111)
- Schools - Akwesasne Freedom School (N.Y.) (Box 111)
- Schools - Albuquerque Indian School (Box 111)
- Schools - Arizona State University (Box 111)
- Schools - Bacone College (Oklahoma) (Box 111)
- Schools - Carlisle Indian Industrial School (PA) (Box 111)
- Schools - Chemana Indian School (Oregon) (Box 111)
- Schools - Cherokee Indian Normal School (N.C.) (Box 111)
- Schools - Cherokee National Seminary (Box 111)
- Schools - Chilocco Indian School (Oklahoma) (Box 111)
- Schools - Community Colleges (Box 111)
- Schools - Cook Christian Training School (Box 111)
- Schools - Cornell University (NY) (Box 111)
- Schools - D.Q. University (Box 112)
- Schools - Dartmouth College (N.H.) (Box 112)
- Schools - Dwight Indian Training School (OK) (Box 112)
- Schools - El Cemi Pottery School (Box 112)
- Schools - Flandreau Indian School (Box 112)
- Schools - Foreign Mission School (Conn.) (Box 112)
- Schools - Fort Sill Indian School (OK.) (Box 112)
- Schools - Fort Yuma Indian School (CA) (Box 112)
- Schools - Hampton Normal and Agricultural Institute (Box 112)
- Schools - Harvard University (Mass.) (Box 112)
- Schools - Haskell Institute (Kansas) (Box 112)
- Schools - He Dog School (Box 112)
- Schools - Hofstra University (N.Y.) (Box 112)
- Schools - Incarnate Word College (Texas) (Box 112)
- Schools - Indian (Box 112)
- Schools - Indian Education Center, Arizona State University (Box 112)
- Schools - Institute of American Indian Arts (N.M.) (Box 112)
- Schools - Intermountain Indian School (Utah) (Box 112)
- Schools - Laurentian University (Box 112)
- Schools - Marty Indian School (Box 112)
- Schools - Mission (Box 112)
- Schools - Mohawk Institute (Canada) (Box 112)
- Schools - Moor's Indian Charity School (Conn.) (Box 112)
- Schools - Native American Educational Services College (Box 112)
- Schools - Navajo Community College (Arizona) (Box 112)
- Schools - North American Indian Traveling College (Box 112)
- Schools - Oglala Lakota College (Box 112)
- Schools - Pembroke State University (Box 112)
- Schools - Pennsylvania State University (Box 112)
- Schools - Phoenix Indian School (Box 112)
- Schools - Pipestone School (Minnesota) (Box 112)
- Schools - Pyramid Lake High School (Nevada) (Box 112)
- Schools - Ramah Navajo High School (N.M.) (Box 112)
- Schools - Ramapo College of New Jersey (Box 112)
- Schools - Red Cloud Indian School (S.D.) (Box 112)
- Schools - Riverside Indian School (Box 112)
- Schools - Rosebud Boarding School (S.D.) (Box 112)
- Schools - Rough Rock Demonstration School (Arizona) (Box 112)
- Schools - Rutgers (New Jersey) (Box 112)
- Schools - Saint Catherine Indian School (N.M.) (Box 112)
- Schools - Saint Francis Indian Mission (Box 112)
- Schools - Saint Joseph's Indian School (Box 112)
- Schools - Saint Labre Indian School (Box 112)
- Schools - San Diego State College (CA) (Box 112)
- Schools - Sanostee (Box 112)
- Schools - Santee Normal Trading School (Nebraska) (Box 112)
- Schools - Saskatchewan Indian Federated College (Canada) (Box 112)
- Schools - School of American Research (N.M.) (Box 112)
- Schools - School of Sacred Arts (Box 112)
- Schools - Sherman Institute (CA) (Box 113)
- Schools - Sinte Gleska College (S.D.) (Box 113)
- Schools - Six Nations Farmers School (NY) (Box 113)
- Schools - Southwestern Indian Polytechnic Institute (NM) (Box 113)
- Schools - Stanford University (CA) (Box 113)
- Schools - Stewart Indian School (Box 113)
- Schools - Survival & Freedom (Box 113)
- Schools - Takini (Box 113)
- Schools - Thomas Indian School (NY) (Box 113)
- Schools - Trent University (Canada) (Box 113)
- Schools - Tribal Colleges (Box 113)
- Schools - Tucson Indian Training School (AZ) (Box 113)
- Schools - University of Arizona (Box 113)
- Schools - University of California (Box 113)
- Schools - University of Florida (Box 113)
- Schools - University of Massachusetts (Box 113)
- Schools - University of Montana (Box 113)
- Schools - University of New Mexico (Box 113)
- Schools - University of Utah (Box 113)
- Schools - University of Wisconsin (Box 113)
- Schools - U.S. Indian Vocational School (Box 113)
- Schools - Virginia (Box 113)
- Sculpture (Box 113)
- Sekani Indians (Box 113)
- Seminole Indians 1 (Box 113)
- Seminole Indians 2 (Box 133)
- Seminole Indians - Bibliography (Box 113)
- Seminole Indians - Clothing and adornment (Box 113)
- Seminole Indians - Economics (Box 113)
- Seminole Indians - Government relations (Box 113)
- Seminole Indians - Health (Box 113)
- Seminole Indians - History (Box 113)
- Seminole Indians - Language (Box 113)
- Seminole Indians - Legal Documents (Box 113)
- Seminole Indians - Social life and customs (Box 113)
- Seminole Indians - Tribal government (Box 113)
- Seneca Indians 1 (Box 113)
- Seneca Indians 2 (Box 114)
- Seneca Indians 3 (Box 114)
- Seneca Indians - Oversize (Box 132)
  Kinzua Dam
- Seri Indians (Box 114)
- Serrano Indians (Box 114)
- Seventh Generation (Box 114)
- Sewee Indians (Box 114)
- Shamans and Shamanism 1 (Box 114)
- Shamans and Shamanism 2 (Box 114)
- Shasta Indians (Box 114)
- Shasta Nations (Box 114)
- Shawnee Indians (Box 114)
- Sheet Music (Box 134)
- Shinnecock Indians (Box 114)
- Shops - Indian Merchandise (Box 114)
- Shoshoni Indians (Box 114)
- Sign Language (Box 114)
- Siksika Indians 1 (Box 114)
- Siksika Indians 2 (Box 114)
- Siouan Indians (Box 115)
- Sioux Indians - Oversize (Box 131)
- Sioux Indians - Artwork - Oversize (Box 131)
- Slavery (Box 115)
- Smallpox (Box 115)
- Smuggling (Box 115)
- Social life and customs 1 (Box 115)
- Social life and customs 2 (Box 115)
- Social life and customs 3 (Box 133)
  Benjamin Bussey Thatcher, Indian traits: being sketches of the manners, customs, and charecter of the North American natives, 1833, photostats.
- Social problems 1 (Box 115)
- Social problems 2 (Box 115)
- Songs (Box 134)
- South America (Box 115)
- South America - Antiquities (Box 115)
- South America - Art (Box 115)
- South America - History (Box 115)
- South America - Indians 1 (Box 115)
- South America - Indians 2 (Box 116)
- South Carolina (Box 116)
- South Carolina - Antiquities (Box 116)
- South Carolina - History (Box 116)
- South Carolina - Indians (Box 116)
- South Dakota - Antiquities (Box 116)
- South Dakota - History (Box 116)
- South Dakota - Indians (Box 116)
- Southern Indians (Box 116)
- Southwest (Box 116)
- Southwest - Antiquities 1 (Box 116)
- Southwest - Antiquities 2 (Box 116)
- Southwest - Antiquities 3 (Box 116)
- Southwest - Antiquities 4 (Box 116)
- Southwest - Antiquities 5 (Box 117)
- Southwest - History (Box 117)
- Southwest - Indians 1 (Box 117)
- Southwest - Indians 2 (Box 117)
- Southwest - Indians 3 (Box 117)
- Southwest - Indians 4 (Box 117)